Missing Delta’s Treasure Month event resulted in a direct loss of 100 million! The official treasure map released,
Did everyone see it? There is a lot of mystery in this picture.
There are twelve treasure points hidden in the No. 0 Dam map. Officials made it clear that
Treasure map No. 8 must have a red dot, and I have found it for everyone. Like and collect,
Just be one step ahead of your brother! As soon as the event starts, rush in!
Treasure No. 1 is located in the underground excavation area of the dam in the middle of the map, roughly at this location.
Treasure No. 2 is located near the mining tower below the cement factory. Treasure number three is located in the pipe behind the barracks.
Near the colorful egg box in Three Cities and Three Courtyards, Treasure No. 4 is located at the entrance of the visitor center in the lower right corner of the map.
There is a high probability that it will be painted near the white container. Treasure point No. 5 is located near the river beach.
It is very likely that it will be painted on the red container or on the ground. Treasure No. 6 is located on the hillside below the wild camp.
There is a high probability that it will be brushed on this box. Treasure No. 7 is located between the top of the dam and the mountainside maintenance station.
There is a high probability that it will be painted on the red container. Treasure No. 8 is located near the container in the rescue building.
There is a high probability that it will be refreshed on the container. Treasure No. 9 is located at the top of the dam.
Treasure No. 10 is located at the foot of the mountain on the right side of the camp, and will most likely be found in the basement room.
Treasure No. 11 is located outside the Administration West Building, near the construction site on the left.
Most likely it will appear at the entrance to the basement or on a box next to it.
Treasure point No. 12 is located in the cement factory, near the entrance of the underground passage.
The above is the approximate location of the No. 0 Dam treasure.
However, the specific refresh mechanism will not be known until the event goes online.